(忆往昔)
西方出现了一位新的领导者
There's a new leader rising in the west.
迪恩  是我  莉莉丝
Hi, Dean. It's me -- Lilith.
我觉得我不再喜欢你了
I don't think I like you anymore.
我将在你头脑里设一道屏障
I'm gonna put up a barrier inside your mind.
不要碰这个屏障
Don't scratch the wall.
也许我不是真实存在的
Maybe I'm not real,
但我哪里也不去  萨姆
but I'm not going anywhere, Sam.
萨姆
Sam!
你们俩这辈子斗妖魔鬼怪
Aren't you full up just playing snuffleupagus
还不够烦的吗
with the devil all the livelong?
我不知道  鲍比
I don't know, Bobby.
我倒无所谓老能看见路西法
Seeing Lucifer's fine with me.
至少我的疯狂还在一定范围之内
At least all my crazy's under one umbrella.
(四年前)
(爱达荷州  科达伦)
海夫洛克女士  你不该过来的
Ms. Havelock, you shouldn't have come.
我要亲眼见见他
I needed to see it for myself --
我们千辛万苦才追踪到他  花了这么长时间
After all that tracking, all those hours we spent.
通过书籍研究他们是一回事  但...
I mean, it's one thing to study them in books. It's...
我闻到了绝经老女人的味道
Do I smell menopause?
这不是西部的那个贱人巫士嘛
Well, if it isn't the wiccan bitch of the west.
海夫洛克女士
Ms. Havelock,
我知道是你帮他们找到我的
I know you're the one that helped them find me.
天啊
My god...
但却没能及时救这个女孩的命
Not in time to save our big girl here,
但你还是立了大功
but still, you get a merit badge.
他们抓到你了  狗娘养的
They caught you, you son of a bitch!
你没法再杀人了
No more murders!
而且你就要重返地狱了
And you're going back to hell.
诺拉  诺拉
Oh, Nora, Nora...
我会像掏空南瓜一样把你掏空
I'm gonna scoop you out like a pumpkin.
你知道吗
You know that?
你掏人的日子结束了  笨蛋
Yeah, your, uh, scooping days are over, gomer.
你现在唯一需要担心的
All you got to worry about now...
就是我们
is us.
你已经不是我们这次打猎抓到的第一个恶魔了
You ain't the first demon we've tracked down on this safari.
没错  事实上
That's right. As a matter of fact,
我觉得你已经是第七个了
I think you put us over half a dozen.
想找莉莉丝  你们根本没找对地方
Looking for Lilith in all the wrong places.
那你得帮帮我们了
Well, you're gonna help us with that.
如果你们要海扁他
If things are about to get messy,
那也许你该见见这具肉身的主人
maybe you should meet the owner of this fleshy temple...
他乖得很
A puppy of a man.
你们会喜欢他的
You'll like him.
杰弗里  杰弗里  是你吗
Jeffrey? Jeffrey, is that you?
天啊  不要
Oh, god. No.
你们得阻止他
You have to stop him.
我们会的  我们会阻止他的
We will. We're going to, okay?
我们会把那个恶魔送回地狱
We're gonna send that demon back to hell.
好
Okay.
拜托不要伤害我
Please don't hurt me.
杰弗里  在我们放他走之前
Jeffrey, before we can let him go...
这个恶魔知道其他同类的下落
Look, the demon knows where we can find more of his kind, okay?
我们在追捕他们  一个都不放
See, we're hunting them -- all of them.
他不会轻易把情报说出来
He's not gonna give up his rolodex easy.
杰弗里  我们要拿刀割他
Jeffrey, we're gonna have to cut into him.
也就是割你
That means you.
他逼我对那些女人下毒手
Oh, the things he made me do to those women.
不管你们要对他做什么
Whatever you have to do...
尽管动手就好
You have to do it.
拜托你们一定要阻止这个恶魔...
Please just stop this evil piece of...
絮絮叨叨  絮絮叨叨
And on and on and on.
说实话  一说起"善恶"什么的
Frankly, he can get tedious
他就变得啰里啰嗦的
with this whole "good and evil" thing.
你说得没错
You know, you were right.
我喜欢杰弗里  他是个好人
I like Jeffrey. He's a decent guy.
事实上  他刚把肉身交给我们处置了
In fact, he just signed off on his temple.
她还有其他手下  我们已经知道了
She's got other lieutenants. We already know that.
把名字告诉我们
We want names.
好吧  好吧
All right! All right!
他叫麦瑞克
His name is Merrick!
我发誓
I swear!
你们能在新奥尔良找到他
You'll find him in New Orleans!
[咒语]
[邪恶力量 第7季第15集]
杰弗里
Jeffrey?
杰弗里  你醒了吗
Jeffrey, you awake?
你刚才晕过去了  你休克了
Hey, you passed out. You're in shock.
他走了吗
He's -- he's gone?
我们把他驱走了
We exorcised him.
尽量别动  好吗
Try not to move, okay?
我们快到医院了
We're almost to the hospital.
你弟弟呢
Your... your brother?
我弟弟留在犯罪现场清除我们的痕迹
My brother stayed back to clean us out of that crime scene.
没必要为杀掉恶魔坐牢吧
There's no reason to go down for a demon's murders.
懂我的意思吧
You know what I mean?
好了  好了  慢慢来
All right. All right, take it easy.
好了  送你到这里  接下来自己能行吧
All right, you're good to make it from here, right?
杰弗里  在急救室不要提恶魔
Okay, Jeffrey, no demon talk in the E.R.,
懂吗
you understand me?
你被打劫了
You were mugged.
好
Okay.
谢谢你
Thank you.
(爱达荷州  科达伦)
(现在)
机密服务器
"Classified server"?
肯定是德弗罗吧
Got to be Devereaux, right?
喂
Hello?
谢天谢地
Thank god.
弗兰克  弗兰克  有什么消息告诉我
Frank, Frank, what do you got for me?
这地方不错
It's nice.
有点像是男洗手间加了几张床
Kind of like a men's room with beds.
鳄梨垢
Hmm, avocado grime.
要用好几年才能长成这样的薄片
Takes years to build up a patina like this.
找不到他是什么意思
What do you mean you can't find him?
那可是迪克·罗曼  看新闻联播就行
It's Dick Roman. Turn on CNN.
你看见他参加菲尼克斯的记者招待会了吗
Didn't you see him at that, uh, press conference in Phoenix?
那混蛋到处跑
The bastard's everywhere.
你确定吗
You sure?
不  我不
No, I-I-I don't.
我才不在乎他们是否渗透了
I don't care that they've infiltrated
豪华游艇产业  弗兰克
the luxury-boat industry, Frank.
好啊  给卡内(美国说唱歌手)打电话吧
Great. Call Kanye.
弗兰克还在查罗曼吗
Frank's still stumped on Roman?
对
Yeah.
好吧  开始干活
All right, let's do this.
好吧  看这些死者的档案
Okay, um, look at the victim profiles --
同样的年龄  发色  身形
same age, same hair color, body type.
仪式中毁尸的方式是一模一样
The ritual mutilations line up exactly.
底下谁会把咱们这些小恶魔放出来啊
Who down there would've let our demon out of the can?
他告了他上司的密  我们确保了这一点
He squealed on his superiors. We made sure of that.
他得等到小号节才能放出来吧
I mean, he should be down under until, uh, trumpet day.
但过去两周有两个女人被杀  丢失同样身体部位
But two women killed in the last two weeks, same parts missing,
而且连他们被杀的地点都没变
I mean, same old hunting grounds, even.
好吧  我们可以过去看看
All right, well, we can take a swing at it.
但你得知道现在咱们的重点在利维坦啊
But you know it's all about the Leviathans now, okay?
他们才是我们最应该被猎杀的
They're the ones we need to be hunting.
对  但不行  现在不行
Yeah, but, no -- I mean, not right now.
这个是咱们的事  迪恩
This one's ours, Dean.
这显然是咱们当时活没做干净
It's unfinished business, apparently.
好吧
All right.
这是32队  重复一遍  是32队
This is unit 32. Repeat, unit 32.
我们又发现一个
We've got another one,
在187号公路上
at 187.
白人女性  快四十岁  在亨利自主干洗店
Femail, caucasian, maybe late 30s, at the Henley Autowash.
32队  增援马上就到
Unit 32, assistance is en route.
这里很不堪  调度中心
Got a real mess here, dispatch.
每次咱们这么干
You know, every time we do this,
我都在想  会不会就在今天
I wonder if today's the day.
我们走过去  向一堆装成警察的大嘴怪
We walk up, flash our tin to a bunch of chompers
亮了徽章
pretending to be policemen.
有同感
I hear you.
我就说你们俩会来
Thought you guys might show up.
是那对好搭档  你们是鲍汉姆探员...
It's the Drummer Boys. Agents, uh, Bonham...
和沃茨探员  对吗
and Watts, right?
对
Yeah.
没错  就是我们
Yeah, absolutely.
很高兴再次见到你  警探...
Uh, it's a pleasure to see you again, Detective...
-萨顿  -不好意思
- Sutton. - You know what? Pardon me.
你叫什么来着
Uh, what was it -- Detective...
是萨顿
Sutton.
没关系  我是萨顿警探
Oh, no problemo, Detective Sutton.
萨顿
Sutton.
萨顿  对  你好
Sutton, yeah. Hi.
真不想这么说  但案子看来又重开了
Sad to say, case looks to be open again.
你确定吗
Are you sure?
同样的工具
Same tools.
同样的伤口  一样疯狂
Same cuts. Same crazy.
倒也说得通
Makes sense.
毕竟我们上次没能抓住这杂种  对吗
I mean, we didn't catch the critter last time, did we?
没有嫌疑犯吗
And no suspects?
跟以前一样
Same as before.
做得十分缜密
Very thorough.
很冷血
Cold-blooded.
谢谢  警探
Thank you, detective.
随时效劳
Anytime.
硫磺
Sulfur.
见鬼
Damn it.
最好去看看海夫洛克
Better go check on Havelock.
就是这了
This is it.
Wiccansweb.com
Wiccansweb.com.
网店而已
Internet mail order.
就是些小把戏  草药  护身符啥的
White magic only herbs and talismans.
只是小把戏吗
You sure about that?
小心点  油漆还没干
Careful, it's still drying.
我在警局里有人
I have a friend at the sheriff's office.
我知道那些最近的谋杀案
I know about all the new murders.
我尽可能的保护我
I'm doing what I can to protect myself.
我还翻译了一些很古老的驱逐魔咒
I'm also translating some very old banishments.
这些...这些很不错
Wow, uh, these are -- these are good.
谢谢  我现在熟络了
Thanks. I've got an affinity.
但当时  在农舍的那晚
But back then, that night in that farmhouse,
我当时管了自己管不了的事
I was in over my head.
我现在知道了  相信我吧
I know that now, believe me.
我会把那活留给你们这样的专业人士的
I will leave all that to the pros.
你帮我们找到了它
Well, you helped track it down.
那可跑了不少腿呢
I mean, it was some solid legwork.
真遇上情况  我其实就只知道
When it came down to it, all I really knew
该去给谁打电话  让他问来
was somebody who knew somebody
我该去找谁要管事的人的号码
who knew the right number to call.
对了  你们现在的号码打不通了
And your number is not working, by the way.
对  我们遇到些
Right, we, uh, we've had
技术问题  电话有毛病
some technical difficulties -- phone issues.
真是个很大的问题
It's a monster problem, really.
那么你有接触到什么吗
So, uh, you haven't had any contact?
接触恶魔吗  没有  谢天谢地
With the demon? No, thank god.
我在这还有些事
I have one or two things to finish in town,
处理完后我就离开
and then I'm leaving.
做得对
Good choice.
-你们找到杰弗里了吗  -谁
- Have you found Jeffrey yet? - Who?
那个当时被恶魔附身的人
The man who the demon possessed.
那个你们差点打死的人
The one you almost beat to death.
对啊  杰弗里
Yeah, Jeffrey.
那可怜的家伙
That poor bastard.
有些恶魔比较感情用事  是吗
Some demons tend to be sentimental, don't they?
如果可以总是喜欢附身同一个人
Always go back to the same host if they can.
这是个线索
It's a start.
我想说说电影频道
I want to talk about Cinemax.
我们都是成年人
We're grown men.
我们付房租  为什么不能有电影频道
We pay rent. Why can't we get Cinemax?
毛片频道
Skinemax.
中止项目的顾问已经谈过这个了
The halfway program advisers have already weighed in on that.
行  行
Fine, fine.
-集体提议也不能...  -我都说行了
- Bringing it up in group is not gon-- - I said fine!
杰弗里
Jeffrey,
今早晚些时候你也有新闻
you have some pretty big going down later this morning.
没错
That's right, I guess.
我今天要去接她
Um, I'm picking her up today.
是条狗  我打算养条救生犬
I'm getting a dog -- a rescue.
我得我为她喷雾  注射疫苗等等
I had to get her spayed and shots and stuff,
但他们说她已经准备好了
but they said she's ready.
杰弗里和我谈过这事
Jeffrey and I talked about this.
他明白养宠物是特权
He understands that pet ownership is a privilege,
不是普通权利
not a right.
他要向组织里所有的人
He's gonna have to show the whole house
证明自己能担起责任
that he can handle the responsibility.
这就是我这么做的意义  对吧  艾伦
And that's what it's all about, right, Alan?
担起责任
Handling it.
你还好吧
You okay there? Huh?
手术很搞笑吧  是吧
Surgery's a bucket of laughs, huh?
你看上去挺好
You look good.
抱歉要给你戴上这个傻气的圆锥套
I'm sorry for the cone of shame,
但我们得防止针脚裂开
but we got to keep these stitches in.
好了  好了
Okay. Okay.
来吧  来吧
Come on. Come on.
你是杰弗里吗
Jeffrey?
是杰弗里吗
好了  好了  你没事了  没事了
Okay. Look, it's okay. You're okay, you're okay.
抱歉
Sorry.
只是为了确认下
Just had to make sure.
确认什么  确认我今天尿裤子了吗
Make sure of what -- that I peed my pants today?
你吓到我的狗了
Aw, you scared my dog.
我们本来不想吓到它
Uh, we did not want to do that.
听着  杰弗  我们得谈谈
Listen, Jeff, we got to, uh, we got to talk.
这...
Well, this is, uh...
我知道这是什么
I know what it is.
我知道你一定过得很艰难
Look, I know it must've been, um, hard.
你听到自己说了什么吗
Do you even listen to yourself?
不打扰了
Oh, don't bother.
你们找我什么
What do you guys want from me?
我们现在确定那个附身过你的恶魔
Well, um, we're pretty sure the demon that possessed you...
又回来了
is back.
什么
What?
你什么意思
What do you mean?
你把他驱逐了  不是吗
You exorcised him, right?
他...他应该在地狱
He's -- he's supposed to be in hell.
杰弗里  冷静点
Jeffrey, look, please just calm down.
请你坐下来
Just have a seat, please.
我不明白
I don't understand.
过去两周又有三位女性遭到谋杀
Three more women have been murdered over the past two weeks.
不  不
No, no.
被害者的调查文件和法医鉴定结果都一样
Same vic profiles, same forensics.
作案现场有硫磺粉末
Crime scene dusted with sulfur.
我们不得不假定是他干的
We've got to assume that it's him.
但现在我们在一起
But we're here now, okay?
如果他来追你
So if he comes after you,
我们会像上次一样困住他
we'll nail him just like we did last time.
她叫什么名字
What was her name?
什么
What?
他杀的最后一个人
The last one he killed.
安娜吗
Uh, Anna?
是安娜·帕克斯顿
Anna Paxton.
马乔丽·威利斯  她是名单里下一个
Marjorie Willis. She's the next one on the list.
名单  什么名单
List? What list?
那个恶魔从前常念叨一份名单
The demon used to recite it all the time,
像背购物单一样
like a grocery list.
那名单印在我脑海里
He burned it in my head --
是所有他要杀害女人的名字
the names of all the women he was gonna kill.
他已经选定受害者了吗
He already had his victims chosen?
还排好了顺序
And put in a line, and in an order.
等等  为什么
Wait. Why?
恶魔不怎么喜欢那种狂热的连环杀手
Demons aren't usually into the obsessive serial-killer crap.
他们更喜欢多种方式作恶
You know, they're more just kind of all-around evil.
他为什么要这么做
Why would he do this?
他说这就是他的工作
He said it was his job.
杰弗里  你的客人登记了吗
Jeffrey, did your, uh, guests sign in?
很抱歉  艾伦
I'm really sorry, Alan.
他们是我还在邮局时认识的朋友
They're friends of mine from my days back at the post office.
我不知道他们要来
I didn't know they were coming.
你怎么想的
So, what do you think?
我们给这可怜的混蛋帮了倒忙
I think we really helped mess this poor son of a bitch up.
你看  他就跟有个公派的保镖一样
Look at him. He's got a state-assigned dad.
好吧  让他们登记离开的时候再签个到
Okay, just get them to sign in when they sign out.
杰弗里  我要去
Uh, Jeffrey, look, I'm gonna go,
我要去找马乔丽·威利斯
uh, I'm gonna go find Marjorie Willis,
暗中保护她  好吗
keep her on watch, okay?
别担心
Don't worry.
我就留在这里  以防万一
I'm gonna stay here just in case.
借过
Excuse me
你说的没错  现在人都不看书了
You're right. We just don't read anymore.
马乔丽·威利斯
Marjorie Willis.
是图书管理员和室内园艺爱好者
Librarian, indoor gardening enthusiast,
也是恶魔的下一位器官捐赠者
our demon's next organ donor.
山姆  拜托和我说说话   都几个月了
Come on, Sam, talk to me. It's been months.
你们把我留在急诊室时
When you left me at the ER,
我断了三根手指
I had three smashed fingers,
少了五颗牙  断了手腕  鼻子
five teeth out, a broken wrist, nose,
颧骨和锁骨
cheekbone, collarbone.
还缝了160针
I had to get 160 stitches.
被抢了
Mugged.
值班医生说
The doctor on duty said it looked like
我像被西班牙宗教法庭审过
I got caught in the Spanish Inquisition.
我们是好人
And we're the good guys.
总的来说他们把我治好了
They patched me up, mostly.
但我丢了工作和健康保险
But I lost my job, my health insurance.
开始酗酒  漂泊  迷失自我
I just started to drink and drift, and I got lost.
都有一点精神崩溃了
Had some kind of mental break.
之后我开始和人交流  聊了聊发生的事
And I started to talk... about what happened.
哥们  别说  永远  都别说
Aw, man. Never tell. Never...never.
我现在知道了  相信我
I know that now, believe me.
让我猜猜
So, let me guess.
从酒池子里到心理评估再到72小时强制拘留
Drunk tank to psych eval to 72-hour forced hold
最后是他们随便选择一个机构把你关在那
to a nice long stay at an institution of their choice.
没错
Yes.
我朋友们就是这样的
It's happened to friends of mine.
有很长一段时间  我都不在乎
For a long time, I didn't care.
真相要比我在哪重要得多
The truth was more important than where I was.
我完全无法应付外面的世界
I was in no shape to cope with the outside world.
你出来了
Well, hey, you got out, you know?
振作起来了
Holding it together.
而现在恶魔却回来了
And now the demon is back.
很遗憾  兄弟
I'm sorry, man.
我说真的  对你的种种遭遇深表遗憾
I mean it-- about all of it, you know?
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
我欠你的  我知道
I owe you for it. I know that.
有很多人帮忙  我现在才振作起来
I owe a lot of people for getting even this far.
我
I...
糟了
Crap.
怎么了
What?
如果他还没有盯上下一个女人  马乔丽
If he isn't already circling the next woman, Marjorie,
那我...我可能知道他在哪
than I- I think I might know where he is.
他有一个特别的地方
He had this special place
用来存放他藏匿地的纪念品
where he kept souvenirs where he nested.
你怎么没告诉我们
Why didn't you tell us this?
我不想去
I didn't want to go.
你不必去  我们会处理的
You don't have to go. We'll handle it.
我得去  我必须得去
I do. I have to.
"平均年降雨量  朴树  德州..."
"Average annual rainfall-- hackberry, Texas..."
拜托  萨姆  关注我一下
Come on, Sam, pay attention to me.
我好无聊哦
I'm bored.
内战迷吗
Civil War buff?
可恶  没信号
Damn it-- no service.
好孩子  你待在这
Good girl. You stay.
这里有些牛肉干
Here's some jerky.
乖乖待着
Stay.
它不会在这里撒尿的  对吧
Thing's not gonna pee in here, is it?
我不知道
Um, I don't know.
他带你到这里
So, he'd get you this far,
然后就不让你看了  是吗
and then he'd shut your lights out, yeah?
不知为何  他对这地方一直遮遮掩掩的
For some reason, he was very secretive about this place.
但过了一会
But after a while,
他只在我们走进去的时候才遮住我的双眼
he'd only really sort of cover my eyes when we walked in.
你觉得你能带我们回到那里吗
Okay, you think you can get us back there?
就在我的这些停产期刊里干我
Right here in my discontinued periodicals.
就是这样
Oh, that's it.
走廊尽头的红色门
Red door down the hallway.
的确有
Yeah, there is.
肯定是这里没错
This must be it.
待在这  好吗
All right, stay over here. Okay?
你就待在这  别动
You just stay here. Don't move.
什么情况
What the hell?
没事的
Hey. Hey, all right.
我们会把你救出去的
We're gonna get you out of here.
我不会伤害你的
Hey, hey, I'm not gonna hurt you, okay?
但你别乱动
But you got to stay still.
我很肯定这人喜欢无聊的胖妞
I'm pretty sure this guy's the boring sort of chubby chaser.
留下你的姓名  电话  以及梦魇
Leave your name, number, and nightmare at the tone.
迪恩  你在哪  我这里一无所获
Dean, where are you? I'm scoping zero out here.
可不是什么好兆头
Not a good sign.
你居然还没注意到  真让我惊讶
Surprised you haven't picked up on that yet.
就在  法医报告里
It's right... there in the coroner's report.
在最近的一件谋杀案中
In this latest round of killings, our big girls
警察在死者血液中发现了大量镇定剂
had traces of heavy tranquilizers in their blood.
但我们的恶魔很强大
Yeah, but our demon's strong enough
足以让那些胖妞做任何他要求的事  对吧
to make fat Betty do whatever he wants to, right?
那他为什么会需要镇定剂呢
So, why does he need the tranqs?
难道是他腿脚不行了吗
Think he's got a bad back?
无论这里发生了什么
Yeah, whatever is going on here,
绝不是恶魔回来杀人了
you know that demon's not coming back to kill anybody.
我是特别探员史密斯
This is Special Agent Smith.
请留下您的姓名  电话
Please leave your name, number--
糟了  迪恩的两只手机都打不通
Oh, no. That's every cellphone Dean's got.
应该总有一个能接到的  对吧
One of them should've picked up, right?
大哥哥也许已经死了
Big brother's probably dead.
闭嘴
Shut up.
他对我说"闭嘴"了
He said "Shut up" to me.
这就是我所说的  萨姆  重新真正地交流
That's what I'm talking about, Sam-- real interaction again.
我很想念这种互动
I miss that.
语带机锋  像绕口令一样地吵架
The rapier wit, the wittier rape.
拜托
Come on.
我会乖乖的
I'll be good.
我甚至会帮你解决
I'll even help you solve
你那神探南茜(美国漫画人物)的谜案什么的
your little Nancy Drew mystery or whatever.
没有便条
No note.
一个手机扰频器
Hmm, a cellphone scrambler.
但亲爱的  这些是违法的
But, Luci, those are illegal.
好好想想  萨姆
Think, Sam.
也许这和迪恩的手机收不到信号有关
Maybe this has something to do with Dean's telephone blackout.
拉丁语  毫无可疑之处呢
Latin-- not suspicious at all.
我从没见过这个咒语
I've never seen this spell before.
对  但你见过这个类型的
No. But you've seen this type.
恶魔召唤咒  为什么呢
Demon summoning-- why?
为什么  为了召唤恶魔  蠢货
Why? To summon a demon, jackass.
开始看是谁写的
Start looking at who.
你什么意思
Okay, what do you mean?
看看这页纸
Look at the page.
-你认识这个笔迹  -我认识这个笔迹
- You know this handwriting. - I know this handwriting.
咦  我的头真疼
Iay, caramami cabeza!
诺拉  停下  冷静
Nora, stop it! Calm down!
这是什么  这是什么
What is this? What is this?
为何杰弗里手中有你手写的恶魔召唤咒
Why did Jeffrey have a demon summoning in your handwriting?
一切都按照他所说  他所计划的进行
Everything's happening the way he said, the way he planned it.
-什么计划  -你帮不上忙
- What plan?! - You can't help --
你改变不了什么
You can't change it.
逼供吧
Hit her.
诺拉  告诉我发生了什么事
Nora, tell me what is going on.
萨姆  搞定她  她知道迪恩出了什么事
Sam, shake her up. She knows what happened to Dean.
让这蠢妇专心思考  行不
Get this stupid cow to focus, will you?
诺拉  听我说
Nora, listen to me!
不论你在怕什么  你现在应该更怕我
Whatever it is, you should be a lot more scared of me right now
因为我离你只有两英寸远  我能逼你开口
because I'm 2 inches away from you, and I can make you talk.
听明白了没
Do you understand me?
是我儿子
It's my son.
他绑架了我儿子
He has my son!
你脑子在想什么啊
What were you thinking?
你当初怎么会想到
I mean, why would you even
要帮恶魔重返人间的
help bring back a demon in the first place?
我没想召回恶魔
Not the demon.
是杰弗里
Jeffrey!
杰弗里
Jeffrey?
很好  你醒了
Good. You're up.
发生了什么  出了什么事
What happened? What's going on?
没人请你来插手
No one asked you to get involved,
来救我  救任何人
to save me, to save anyone.
什么
What?
你有没有想过也许我挺爱被恶魔附身的
Did you ever think that maybe I loved being possessed?
想过吗
Did you?
我爱那种联系  那种力量
I loved the connection, the power.
我也爱他
And I loved him.
事实上  他是我此生挚爱
Love of my life, actually.
你一定是在开玩笑
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
他解放了我
He liberated me --
带我走向人生真正的使命
started me on my true life mission.
原来是你杀了那些女人
So you're the one with the thing for all those women.
不是吗  杰弗里
Aren't you, Jeffrey?
你是个连环杀手
You're a serial killer.
他找上我之前  我一文不值
I was nothing before he found me --
像一道影子  害怕完成自己使命
A shadow too scared to do what I was brought here to do,
害怕展现自己真实的潜力
too timid to live up to my true potential.
那发生了什么
So, what happened --
红发魔鬼让你吃饱穿暖了吗
Redheaded mommy make you stuff birds, put on dresses?
你不应该无视他人的痛苦
You shouldn't trivialize other people's pain.
所以  就让魔鬼进驻
So, demon comes along,
在你脑海中协同指挥
rides co-pilot in your skull...
教你怎样杀人
teaches you how to kill.
那个名单  是你拟的
The list... that's yours.
多少年来  这只是个我玩的游戏
For years, it was just a game I would play.
每当我在街上与某人擦肩而过
Every time I'd walk by one of them in the street
或者在邮递路上看到某人
or see one on my mail route...
她们的脑海里总会发出一个声音
there's a sound that comes from their brains.
你知道吗
You know that?
只有我能听见  就像邪恶的汽笛声
Only I can hear it, like an evil, little steam whistle.
每当我遇上一个  我就会跟踪她
Every time I saw one, I'd follow her,
记录下她的地址
take down her address.
但我不会做任何事
But I was never gonna do anything,
在他出现之前不会
not till he came along.
他是我的救星
He's the one who saved me.
而你却将他打回地狱
And you sent him to hell.
驱魔之后  我一直严密监视杰弗里
I kept tabs on Jeffrey after the exorcism.
我甚至在医院给他发过护理包
I even sent him care packages in the hospital,
但他从来没回应我
but he never responded.
不久以前  他来找我
And then not long ago, he came to me.
他看起来很健康  精神正常
He seemed healthy, put together, except he wanted to know
但他知道是否有重新召回恶魔的方法
if there was a way to summon the demon back.
他说他已经做了一些调查
He said he'd been doing some research.
大部分都是废话  但他坚信那是可能的
It was mostly nonsense, but he was convinced it was possible.
你还真打开了她的话匣子
You really knocked the cork out of her piehole.
我把他打发走了
I sent him away.
我让他去找其他帮助
I told him to get some more help.
第二天
The next day
他给我打电话
he called me.
让我儿子和我说话
He put my son on the phone.
他把他从宿舍绑架走了
He had taken him from his dorm room.
我向他交待了一切
I gave him everything --
所需的仪式和魔符
the ritual, the sigils.
但他还是不放我儿子
But he kept my boy.
之后他寄给我这个
And then he sent me this.
那是我宝贝儿子的耳朵
It's my baby's ear.
仪式没成功  所以他割下我儿子的耳朵
He cut it off because the ritual didn't work.
那个恶魔交待了一些绝对机密对信息
That demon gave up some serious state secrets --
现在他肯定被严密控制着
Would've gone into big lockdown now.
想召唤他出来可不容易
Not so easy to bring him back up.
杰弗里不管
Jeffrey didn't care.
他让我找到失败的原因  否则要我好看
He told me to find out what went wrong or else.
终于  我找到了一条肯定
Finally, I found a summoning spell
能成功的召唤咒语
that would work for sure.
之后  他说我还有另一项任务
And that's when he said I had another job to do.
是什么
Which was what?
当你们到来后  我得把你们引向杰弗里
When you came, I was supposed to send you to Jeffrey.
他用尸体引路  确保你们会被吸引来
He left a trail of bodies to make sure of it.
"驱魔人之血"
"Blood of the exorcist"?
这是我见过最强的召唤咒
Strongest summoning I've ever seen.
需要当初放逐魔鬼的驱魔人的血
Requires the blood of the exorcist who banished him --
那人就是你哥哥
Your brother.
明白了吗
You see?
这都在杰弗里计划之中
It is all part of Jeffrey's plan.
是啊  好了  新计划
Yeah. Well...new plan.
追踪咒  不管是巴伐利亚式还是埃及式
Tracking spell -- Bavarian, Egyptian.
我不在乎  你来选择
I don't care -- dealer's choice.
用被追踪人的肉体来找到他和迪恩
Use the flesh of the body to find the body and Dean.
你想留着这耳朵  还是你儿子
Do you want the ear or the kid?
你吓得我毛骨悚然
You're giving me the chills.
我想我挺了解你的
I like to think I know you pretty well.
是吗  你怎么知道的
Yeah, how do you figure?
我看着你折磨无辜者  逼出恶魔
I watched you torture an innocent man to get out a demon.
场面惊心动魄  很能反映人性
Pretty charged situation... revealing.
你们夸夸其谈  展现出了很多个性
You guys talked about a lot, showed a lot of character.
上帝啊
God...
你绞尽脑汁想要拯救这个世界
You were so desperate to fix the world back then.
而人们又在不断遭受痛苦
It kills you...
这几乎让你生不如死
that people keep getting hurt...
但你对此又无能为力
and you just can't stop it.
我是不是应该说你已经生不如死了  是吗
Or I should say it's killed you, shouldn't I?
去死吧
You know what? Screw you.
我当时在场啊
Hey. I was there.
我是那么的绝望  迪恩  因为他离开了
I was depressed, Dean, because he was gone.
我就像一具没有灵魂的残骸  一个醉鬼
I was a wreck, an emotional shell, a drunk.
我甚至自杀过
I was suicidal.
通常我不推荐别人自杀
I don't usually endorse suicide,
但是老兄  为什么你没成功
but man, what stopped you?
因为大楼里的艾伦阻止了我
It was Alan at the house.
开什么玩笑
You're kidding me.
他真的是一名很好的精神康复医师
He's a really good rehab therapist.
让我重新认识到了我的目标  端正了我的态度
Really helped me focus on my goals, my attitude.
我不得不说
I have to say,
我确实从他的疗程中获益匪浅
I really benefited from the whole program.
一个人的幸福生活
A life well-lived
来源于对真正快乐的不懈追求
comes from the structured pursuit of meaningful happiness.
我认识到如果没有恶魔  我什么也不是
I realized I was nothing without my demon.
因此我决定让他回来
Then I decided I have to get him back.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
宝贝儿  过来
Hey, there, honey. Come on.
我承认  这菜谱确实有点恶心
It's a bitch of a recipe, I must admit.
不是吧
No.
你这狗娘养的变态
Oh, you sick son of a bitch.
你好  杰弗里
Hello, Jeffrey.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester.
我又一次
As I live and breathe...
回到了这个世界
Again.
你干嘛
What are you doing?
我在感谢你呢  杰弗里
I'm thanking you, Jeffrey.
你为什么附身在这半死的躯体上
What are you doing with this half-dead piece of crap?
来我身上
Come into me.
我们度过了一段很美妙的时光  是吗  杰弗里
We had a very special time together, didn't we, Jeffrey?
你还记得我教你的东西  多么令人欣慰啊
It warms my heart to see you haven't forgotten what I taught you.
你学以致用
You built on it.
抓到了一个温彻斯特
You captured a Winchester.
杰弗里你是我的好学生
You, Jeffrey...my pupil.
我不想当你的学生  我想成为你的一部分
I don't want to be your pupil. I want to be yours.
但我不需要你了
But I'm done with you.
我的任务完成了
My work is finished.
你现在可以自由地想干嘛干嘛去了
You can do everything now, all on your beautiful own.
不
No.
No?
我们的字典里没有"不"  记得吗  杰弗里
We don't do "No." Remember, Jeffrey?
继续锯你的绳子吧  累了记得休息
Keep sawing away at your ropes, Penelope Pitstop.
如果你喜欢  我可以解开它跟你跳舞
We can dance standing up if you want.
这就是你干的好事
So, is this what you do --
让好好的一个的邮递员变成疯子
find postal workers, make 'em go postal?
我只是稍微指点了下而已
I talent scout. That's all.
我在他们下地狱之前
Looking for the next generation of superstars...
就发觉了他们的潜力  比如杰弗里
before they get to hell, like Jeffrey here.
他有着所有的潜质  如同瓶子里的泡泡
He had all the raw material... just bubbling in there.
我要做的只是简单的打开瓶口
All I had to do was loosen the lid on his jar,
简单的做几个示范
show him some practical know-how.
那这个孩子呢
Yeah, what about the kid?
这个吗
This one?
没有前途
I don't think.
没有什么用
Not much to work with.
没有潜质
No natural gift.
我或许会在去拉斯维加斯的路上毁掉这个躯壳
I'll probably burn this meat off on my way to Vegas.
真他妈见鬼
You've got to be kidding me!
离开我的儿子
You let go of my son!
你们是哪儿冒出来的
Where do you keep coming from?
咒语
Exorcizamus te, omnis immundus spiritus.
他会回来的  黑暗式的回归
He'll be back, you know. Back in black.
下地狱吧
Go to hell.
[咒语]
妈妈
Mom?
没事了
I got you.
没事了孩子
I got you, baby.
天啊
Oh, god.
杰弗里只是假装成受害者
So, Jeffrey was just pretending to be the victim.
在农场房子里面的那场驱魔
Way back in that farmhouse during the exorcism,
他只是在演戏
he-he was just...acting.
他是个精神病  萨姆
He was a psychopath, Sam.
他们最常干的是就是演戏
That's what they do all the time, is act.
装的自己是个正常人
Act like they're normal,
装的他们不是那么疯狂
Act like they're not balls-to-the-wall crazy.
你要睡觉了吗
You going to sleep?
废话  去他妈的良心  这就是我说的
Damn straight. Screw consciousness, that's what I say.
不  萨姆  你可不能睡
No, no, Sam. No nap for you, Sammy.
得了吧  别这样
Oh, come on, don't do that.
我们谈谈吧
Let's talk, Sam.
我一直非常喜欢我们的小对话
I always enjoyed our special little chats.
你不想谈谈吗
Don't you want to talk?
看那
Yeah, look at that.
事情肯定有所不同了  不是吗
Something's definitely different now, isn't it?
你让我进去了
You let me in.
你想要我  伙计
You wanted me, partner.
现在你以为还能用你小小的伎俩
So you think you can use your little tricks
再一次放逐我吗  不行了
to banish me again like that? No.
我确信我搞定你了  小伙计
I do believe I've got you, bunk buddy.
看看我怎么用我的小魔术搅和你的思想吧
Got my finger wiggling around in your brainpan.
来吧  小萨姆  来吧
Come on, Sammy! Come on!
跟我一起说
Say it with me now.
早安  越南
Good morning, Vietnam!